It is important to think about needs versus wants.
考虑需求与需求是很重要的
As you learn about the capabilities of AWS for reliability and redundancy,
当您了解 AWS 的可靠性和冗余能力时
it is important to consider what level of
重要的是要考虑
availability is required for a use case or environment.
对于用例或环境 可用性是必需的
Some non-critical cases require no redundancy,
一些非关键的案例不需要冗余
while production environments typically require significant levels of redundancy.
而生产环境通常需要大量冗余
In most cases, redundancy has cost.
在大多数情况下 冗余都有成本
Depending on the services you use,
根据您使用的服务
redundancy can cost a lot.
冗余可以花费很多
Typically, redundancy costs at least double.
通常 冗余成本至少为两倍
For example, in RDS,
例如 在 RDS中
take the instance cost and double it to have a hot standby,
把它的成本和双倍的成本提高到一个热备用
triple it to have a read replica in another region.
使它在另一个区域中具有读副本
Review the cost structure for what you're
查看您的成本结构
building and weigh the costs against the benefits.
将成本与收益进行权衡
Keep in mind that cost comes in multiple forms: there is direct monetary expense,
请记住 成本采用多种形式: 有直接的货币开支
as well as the cost of complexity,
以及复杂性的代价
which can take the form of higher learning curves or
可以采用更高学习曲线的形式
difficulty in monitoring a system or diagnosing a problem.
难以监控系统或诊断问题
When considering how to architect a service,
在考虑如何设计服务时
you should think about how a disruption
你应该想想
or data loss in that service would impact your business.
或者该服务中的数据丢失会影响您的业务
You'll need to think about what it will take to restore service,
你需要考虑一下恢复服务需要什么
as well as the contractual obligations to which your business has committed.
以及您的业务所承担的合同义务